womf.com 2011-04-13

# - Privacy Policy

## WOMF USA, LLC's Commitment to Online Security

Personal information is accessible only by staff designated to handle online submissions.

## Personal Information that WOMF USA, LLC may collect online

When visiting the WOMF website and signing up for products, services or information through any website page, you may choose to supply WOMF with information that identifies you personally. This information may include your name and contact information, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, and other information.

WOMF USA, LLC does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 18, we will delete that information from our systems.

WOMF USA, LLC will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

We provide links to third-party sites. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites.

## E-mail

We use e-mail links located throughout the website to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We will use your e-mail address to respond directly to these questions or comments. WOMF USA, LLC considers e-mail transmitted through our website to be private correspondence between the sender and recipient. Therefore, we will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of your private communications to any party outside of WOMF USA, LLC.

The e-mail addresses that you supply to use this service will not be used for any other purpose without your consent.

Except as permitted by this policy, WOMF USA, LLC does not send unsolicited e-mail.

All updates to this policy will be posted here. Last update: February 2010
